Once a forecast adapter works, we want to modify it so
that it can return a second item view type for the
today list item. Normally in the sub class, getViewTypeCount return to
one, but we're going to override it so it returns two for
the two different layouts. But how does it know when to
use one there or the other? Well, we override getItemViewType so
that when the position in the list is zero, then we
say that it's the TODAY view type. Otherwise, it's the FUTURE_DAY
view type. These two view types are declared up
above. These are just integer representations of the view type.
The numbering has to start at zero because these values
can not be greater than or equal to getViewTypeCount. So,
the possible values for us are zero and one,
so that we know that zero always maps to the
view_type_today and that one always maps to view_type_future_day. We're going to
use this information in the new View method. Remember that
previously we inflated the list_item_forecast.xml. Now, we're going to use
the getItemViewType to determine whether we should use one
layout or the other. Fill in the to do
to address this behavior. LayoutId refers to resource ID,
which is in the form of r.layout.something. We don't
have to reform the bindView method because it will
continue to work. That's because the IDs are the
same between the today layout and the future day layout.
This is what your app should look like when you're
done. The today layout is different from the rest of the
days. Go ahead and make these changes in your app and
then finish the To Do. Check this box when you're done.